[
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Who am I?",
    "back": "I am ME"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Roman roads still stand to this day. over thousand years later.",
    "cloze": "roads"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "The Roman Empire was founded in the year 27 AD.",
    "cloze": "27"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "The Sex Pistols were most known for their lead singer Sid Vicious and his girlfriend Nancy.",
    "cloze": "Sex Pistols"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Rainbows are made of love and cotton candy spun from the dreams of these",
    "back": "Unicorns"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "CBGB is famous for what?",
    "back": "Finding many famous groups like Blondie and the Ramones."
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Ceasar was assassinated by his fellow senators in 44 BC.",
    "cloze": "Ceasar"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Hadrian's Wall was a Roman wall built in Britain.",
    "cloze": "Hadrian's Wall"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "What year did the battle of Poitiers occur?",
    "back": "726"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "The Roman Empire spanned",
    "back": "From Britain to the Middle East."
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "The year Rome fell.",
    "back": "476 AD"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Roman emperor known for setting fires.",
    "back": "Nero"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "The Dead Milkmen was known for its punk sensibilities but hilarious songs like \"Take me to the specialist\"",
    "cloze": "Dead Milkmen"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Romans pioneered this utility:",
    "back": "Public works and sewage management"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Aquaducts were a Roman innovation to transport fresh water to the public.",
    "cloze": "Aquaducts"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "The Roman Collosseum was a place where emperors staged sea battles, fed its enemies to lions, and other public spectacles to distract and control the people.",
    "cloze": "Collosseum"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "This punk group was well known for its highly political lyrics and songs coupled with insane punk rhythms. ",
    "back": "Dead Kennedys"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "John Lennon is the walrus.",
    "cloze": "John Lennon"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "The Misfits and DRI represent this musical genre from the 1980s.",
    "back": "Punk"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Electric sheep dream of robot dogs on treadmills. ",
    "cloze": "Electric"
  }
]